"It seems today that all you see
"Is violence in movies and sex on TV
"But where are those
good old-fashioned values
"On which we used to rely?
"Lucky there's a family guy
"Lucky there's a man who positively
can do all the things that make us
"Laugh and cry
"He's a family guy
On the whole, I enjoy my job as a pharmacist.
In fact, many of my customers
are your mommies and daddies.
Jimmy, your mother had awful postpartum
depression after you were born.
And, Danielle, your father had very bad
haemorrhoids that stung him unmerciful.
They were awful. They were like
stinky little balloons. Ugh!
I gave him some special ointment,
and he hurt so bad that he had to
apply it in the car with his sock.
Thank you.
- Cool! I wanna be a pharmacist!
- Yeah!
Thank you, Mr Goldman.
Our final speaker is Mr Griffin.
- Yeah!
- Hey, kids! You know what I do?
I work at a toy factory.
And you know what I do there?
I bet you're just a low-level
assembly-line guy
who stands all day
screwing heads on dolls.
"Ooh, is it on straight?"
"I don't know. " Boo!
- Why, you snot-nosed...
- Mr Griffin!
He plays in the park. Get him there.
Does anyone have any questions?
Can we listen to the claims adjuster again?
Yeah!
Welcome back to Quahog Five News.
Here's Ollie Williams with
the "Black You" weather forecast.
- It's gonna rain!
- Thanks, Ollie.
Finally, we go to Asian reporter
Tricia Takanawa,
interviewing a guy
from the Renaissance Fair.
Thanks, Tom. Sir, for those who
aren't familiar with the tradition,
tell us about the Renaissance Fair.
Yea. But first, bride of Genghis,
thou must explainest to me
thy very peculiar electronic wand.
Whoooooo!
Rupert, are you ready to hear our "mad lib"?
Ahem. "Cinderella had three
wicked step-watermelons
who were very smelly to her. "
"So her fairy god-toilet turned
a pumpkin into a fanny
and sent her off to the poop. "
Oh, my! How ruthlessly absurd.
Peter, how was your presentation
to Chris's class?
- It was a waste of time.
- It couldn't have been that bad.
I was terrible. Everyone else had an important
job and was way more successful than me.
Come on. You... You have a great job.
Yeah. You're... you're doing...
you're doing good.
If you're not satisfied,
then be more assertive.
Invite Mr Weed to dinner
and show him what you have to offer.
I guess I could. I just hope it goes OK.
We've had bad luck with guests.
Remember Margot Kidder?
We loved you in the Superman movies.
You were just wonderful.
Aaghhh!
Mr Weed, I, uh... was wondering
if maybe you'd like to come to
my house for dinner Friday night.
- That wasn't so hard.
- What time?
- 7.30, 8.00?
- Fabulous! What shall I bring?
Calm down. Everything will be fine.
If I blow this, I'll have to go back to
my old job at The Electric Company.
- Duh...
- Ot.
Dot.
- Buh...
- Et.
- Bet.
- Bet. I knew that. Slow down.
- Puh...
- It.
- Pit.
- Pit. Come on, it's my first day.
- Fuh...
- At.
- Fat.
- Oh, that's it, buddy!
That must be him.
Oh, God. I hope I don't get so nervous
I can't control the volume of my voice.
Hello, Peter. How are you?
Fine! Please come in.
It's so nice to have you over, Mr Weed.
Thank you, Mrs Griffin. I understand
you have a beautiful family.
We do. But the children won't be
joining us for dinner. It's their bedtime.
- State your names.
- Meg!
- Chris!
- And I'm Liesl.
The Griffin children would like
to say good night to you.
Mmmm. Who would think that
a woman with such beauty
would have the culinary skills
of Emeril Lagasse?
Well, thank you.
Bam!
Ahem. Peter, don't you have
something to say to Mr Weed?
Oh, yeah.
Mr Weed, I don't care what the guys at work
say. I don't think you're an effeminate weirdo.
Uh, so, what kind of a name is "Weed"?
They gave it to my grandfather
on Ellis Island.
Our original name was Bermuda Grass.
Peter, being here with your wonderful
family, your beautiful home
and your funny talking dog...
well, I'm impressed.
Starting Monday, I'd like to promote you
to head of toy development.
Holy crap! Oh, thanks, Mr Weed!
You won't be sorry.
Brian, quit it. You're embarrassing me.
Brian's choking!
Do the Heimlich manoeuvre, quick!
He's dead.
Aaagh! Aaagh!
I forgot my purse. Aaaghhh!
Let's not panic.
Nobody even knows about this yet.
Police! Random dead-body search!
- Oh, my God! Stall 'em!
- Peter, what are you doing?
Just stall 'em, Lois!
Ha-ha! Gotcha! It's just me - Death.
I'm here for the body.
Ah. Peter, it's OK. It's just Death.
Ah, thank God.
- Did someone choke on a roll in here?
- No, no, no. I spit it up.
Oh.
Our top story:
Doreen, I lost your phone number.
We met at the Sky Lounge
last night. Call me.
In other news, toy industrialist
Jonathan Weed was found dead
in the home of an employee
who claims Weed choked on a roll.
No charges will be filed against
the employee, but the roll is in custody.
I'd do her, do her, wouldn't do her.
Ech, who hasn't done her? Do her.
Lose the pigtails and we'll talk.
Do her, do her...
And now, the last man to see Jonathan Weed
alive has offered to say a few words.
Good afternoon.
As you know, we of the Christian faith
believe that Jesus is not really dead,
but that he must let
the world think he is dead
until he can find a way to control
the raging spirit that dwells within him.
Anyway, before he died, Mr Weed
promoted me to head of toy development.
I brought my attorney who confirms
that this constitutes a verbal contract.
Isn't that right, Saul?
"Yes, sir. " Thank you.
Glad you all found your way
from the cemetery.
I'm Mr Weed's lawyer. We found this tape
among Mr Weed's personal effects
with instructions that it be screened
immediately after his funeral. Enjoy.
Good morning. Camera time.
- Turn that off. I don't have my face on yet.
- You want to tell us what you're making?
It's just a couple of eggs with
the peppers left over from last night.
- Mm...
- Yes.
OK, playtime is over.
Turn it off, monkey, OK?
Ahem.
Hello, friends. If you are watching this,
I am dead, and I bet you're pretty bummed.
- But I have good news.
- Yeah?
The Happy-Go-Lucky Toy Factory
shall be torn down
to make way for the Happy-Go-Lucky
Terminal Disease Institute.
- What?!
- The demolition will begin in... now.
OK, we've got your typing test here
and all the pertinent data
about your, um...
um, you know, your background
and, um... skills and...
- And?
- I gotta be honest with you.
I only have another week and a half here,
and I have completely checked out.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Well, what should I do?
Um...
Chef?
Sorry, we're out of towels.
Let me get that for you, sir.
I should pay two bucks for stickers
cos this guy can't hear? Come on!
Hey, I might be deaf, but I have feelings!
Oh, uh... I mean, what?
- Has Dad found a permanent job yet?
- He's going through a career transition.
He's sampling a few things, searching
for something that fits him just right.
- Clearly it's not that tube top.
- Looking for a good time, sweet cheeks?
- Oh, my God.
- Peter, get in the car!
OK, but it'll cost ya.
You want a Cleveland Steamer?
Get in the car...
What's a Cleveland Steamer?
- It means he'll...
- Whoa, be cool.
Yes, you go to Maple Street,
and then take a left, and then you go...
- So you want to party or what?
- Get in right now!
It's eerie, isn't it?
Like looking into the future.
- Forgetful Freddy was so forgetful...
- How forgetful?
He was so forgetful, whenever he tried
to remember a name, he drew a... "blank".
This is all my fault. If I hadn't pushed you
so hard to invite Mr Weed to dinner,
he'd still be alive and you'd have your job.
We'll get through this.
We just have to scrimp a little.
Sell some stuff we don't really need.
- This'll bring in a couple of bucks.
- Peter, listen.
When we got married, you always talked
about your dream job. Remember?
You put that dream aside
in order to provide for this family.
- Yeah.
- I've saved some money from teaching piano,
and this is the perfect time
for you to pursue that dream.
- Really?
- Yes!
Wow. Since money's tight, I was gonna
suggest that we eat the kids.
Jokingly at first, but then
I was gonna gauge your reaction.
If you were cool with it, we could go
from there. But this is a much better idea!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna realise my dream!
I am gonna be a Renaissance Fair jouster!
Oh, Peter!
Aaaghhh!
This is so exciting!
My little jouster's first day.
- Here's your lunch.
- Thanks, honey. Aw, egg salad!
- Have a good time.
- I'll try.
- Hey, Mort.
- Oh, God! Don't hurt me!
- Oh, hi, Peter.
- You gonna be a jouster, too?
Yes. I'm trying to overcome
my fear of swords
because a man in a pirate suit
stabbed me in the ear when I was five,
and then again when I was 30.
And you? The same?
Nah, not really. It kinda
all goes back to when I was 18.
I was going through that rebellious phase,
and I was hanging out with a bad crowd.
Here, Peter. Try one of these.
- What is it?
- It's a cheeseburger.
Now I know it wasn't a cheeseburger.
But at that time,
I was ready to believe anything.
I didn't know what was going on.
I wandered around and ended up
at the Renaissance Fair.
- I can fly!
- Oh, my God!
I was saved by the one and only Black
Knight of the Quahog Renaissance Fair.
A word of advice. The path to knighthood
is paved with strength and nobility,
not LSD and sideburns.
And from that moment on, I knew
someday I wanted to be a knight like him.
Mercy! I was once addicted
to antihistamines.
I took so many, I thought I was Mr Peanut.
Yeah, that's a great story, too.
So, you think you got
what it takes to be jousters!
If you're gonna joust, you gotta want it!
Let me hear your war cry!
Is that the best you got, you pile of crap?
Yes. From an early age,
my parents discouraged loud noises.
You're a candy-ass maggot!
- Something funny, maggot?
- No, sir!
- You love the Middle Ages, don't you?
- Sir, yes, sir!
The concept of a geocentric universe
gets you sexually excited, doesn't it?
Yes, sir!
You want to make 16th-century
mathematician Johannes Kepler your bitch?
Sir, yes, sir!
- Welcome, apprentices.
- It's him.
Look alive. Allow me to introduce the best
of the best, the Black Knight himself!
And this is his trophy wench,
Maid Madeleine.
Ding!
- Excuse me, Mr Black Knight.
- I'm busy.
I just wanted to thank you. I don't know
if you remember, but when I was a kid,
you helped me get my life back on track.
Agh! Dammit! Look, I'm busy, all right?
- OK, I'll come back later.
- Damn rookies.
Are all the other men
out of the shower yet?
Hey, porker. Yes, I'm calling you a porker,
and there's nothing you can do about it
because I'm protected by my
impenetrable cereal-box fort. Ha-ha-ha!
Hey, you! Drunkie.
Yes, I'm calling you drunkie, and
there's nothing you can do about it...
Agh!
- The toast is ready.
- I'll get it, Lois.
Here you go.
Maybe you shouldn't bring
your lance to the table.
If I'm gonna impress the Black Knight,
my lance must be with me at all times.
You guys will be so proud
when you see me on that field.
Excuse me. I gotta go practise.
Oh, my God, Dad, my earring!
Dad, stop! Argh!
Two mutton joints, please.
Oh, thou wishest to feast on
the appendage of a humble ovine.
Listen, freak. We don't all watch Frasier.
Now give me two mutton joints.
Thank you.
'Tis a glorious afternoon.
Wouldst thou not agree?
Uh, yea, kind shrew.
Uh, I before thee... except after C.
Wouldst thou take a gander
underneath my frock?
Uh, sure. Whatever floats your boat.
There you go.
Frickin' perverts.
Madeleine, go wait in the Hyundai!
What were you doing with my girl?
She walks over here and asks me to put a bird
in her panties! I'm going "What the hell?"
Oh, God! Peter, play dead!
Curl up in an ass ball or something!
- What's the problem, BK?
- I don't like you.
And I don't like you hanging around my girl.
I don't ever want to see you here again.
Oh. OK, but we can see each other
outside the fair, right?
- I'm just trying to understand the rules.
- If I see you again, I'll kill you!
OK, that's much clearer.
Oh, God! I think I just miscarried!
What are you doing? I spent hours
soldering that costume for you.
I don't need it any more. I quit the team.
You can't quit jousting.
The big meet is today. I thought...
Did you just say "big meat"?
Oh, my God, I did.
- We almost missed that.
- That was a close one.
But I'm being serious here. We were
all set to come see you joust today.
You were so excited to be
on the field with the Black Knight.
I'll be watching him from the stands,
because the Black Knight is a big jerk,
just like that guy who fixed our vacuum.
There you go. All fixed.
A half-eaten meatball was
clogging up the intake.
- Oh. Well, did you save it?
- Uh, no.
You bastard.
It's an exciting day here at
the Renaissance Fair, wouldn't you say, Tom?
It would be if you didn't remind us all
of our grandmother's cleavage.
Let's go to the field, where the Black Knight
prepares to challenge his opponent.
"Ohh...
"Hey
Hey, how you doing there, big guy?
You holding up all right?
You want a soda? Hm?
Oh, screw it. I tried.
The Black Knight's next challenger
is Sir Mort Goldman.
Oh, God! I forfeit!
That's it. The Black Knight is out of
challengers and is once again undefeated.
Hey, what's your fat ass doing here?
He's my only means of conveyance.
- But I guess I do spoil him.
- Clearly you do.
And what are you doing here, Griffin?
I told you never to come here again!
- I don't want any trouble.
- You've got trouble if you don't beat it.
- Listen, buddy...
- I said get lost!
- Where's he going?
- Let him go, kids.
You see that, kids?
Your father's nothing but a fizzle!
Nobody calls me a fizzle
and gets away with it!
Except that guy who called me a fizzle
and then ran off. He got away with it.
But most people who call me that
don't get away with it.
Actually, that guy was the only one
who ever called me a fizzle.
After today, only half the people who called
me a fizzle will have gotten away with it.
A new challenger has entered the field.
The crowd has fallen deathly ill.
Silent. Sorry.
Oh, my God, I'm gonna die!
To the owner of a yellow Hyundai,
your car is being towed.
What?
I won!
- Peter, that was amazing. You were so brave.
- Nice going, Dad.
Boy, that was lucky about the car.
Take that, you bastard! Nobody
makes a fool out of Mort Goldman!
Spectacular, maggot! How'd you like
to travel with us as our lead jouster?
Thanks, but no thanks, Coach.
I've lived my dream.
And besides, my life is here with my family.
But, Mom, what's Dad gonna do for a job?
Lt'll be OK, Chris. Remember
that episode of The Honeymooners
when Ralph lost his job but didn't get it back?
Yeah, why was that?
That bugged the crap out of me.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru